Guide to the Thomas C. Moser Papers SC0709
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2008-185
  - Incoming Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Incoming Correspondence, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Incoming Correspondence, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Incoming Correspondence, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Incoming Correspondence, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Incoming Correspondence, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Incoming Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Incoming Correspondence (Holiday Cards & Letters), 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence & Notes (Miscellaneous), 1949-1973 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence-Williams College, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence-Scholastic Magazines re Lord Jim, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence-Victorian Studies, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence-Voice of America re Look Homeward, Angel, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence-Norman G. Jensen, Inc., 1962 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence-Salary, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Incoming Correspondence from Albert Guerard, undated & 1950-1960 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Incoming Correspondence from Albert Guerard, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Incoming Correspondence from Albert Guerard, 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Incoming Correspondence from David Levin, 1960-1964 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Incoming Correspondence from David Levin, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Incoming Correspondence from Jack Hawkes, 1957-1967 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Incoming Correspondence from Bernard Meyer, 1958-1963 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Incoming Correspondence from Bernard Meyer, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Incoming Correspondence from John Miller, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Incoming Correspondence from Patrick Quinn, 1957-1964 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Incoming Correspondence from Yvor Winters, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Incoming Correspondence from Will Stone, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Incoming Correspondence from family, 1960s (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Incoming Correspondence from D.B. Chipp, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1990-1996 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1997 (1 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1997 (2 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1998 (1 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1998 (2 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1999 (1 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1999 (2 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Personal Correspondence, 2000-2003 (1 of 5) (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Personal Correspondence, 2000-2003 (2 of 5) (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Personal Correspondence, 2000-2003 (3 of 5) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Personal Correspondence, 2000-2003 (4 of 5) (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Personal Correspondence, 2000-2003 (5 of 5) (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Personal Correspondence, 2003-2005 (1 of 2) (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Personal Correspondence, 2003-2005 (2 of 2) (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Personal Correspondence and Clippings, 1964-1998 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Stanford University (General) & English Department (Misc.), 1994-2002 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Stanford University (General) & English Department (Misc.), 1994-2002 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Stanford University Continuing Studies-Faulkner Course, 1994-2002 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (including recommendation letters), 1984-1989 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence (including recommendation letters), 1993-1995 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (including recommendation letters), 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence (including recommendation letters), 1998-2005 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Estate of Marjorie K. Kempton, 1968-1997 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Maclin Bocock Guerard, Correspondence and Memorial, 1971-2003 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Ford’s Letters to Oliver Garnett and her Father, 1890s-1900s (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Faulkner Related Titles (book lists) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - “Sergey Stepniak and the Diary of Olive Garnett,” Master Copy (1 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - “Sergey Stepniak and the Diary of Olive Garnett,” Master Copy (2 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - First Draft: Faulkner and His Muse, I. (1 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - First Draft: Faulkner and His Muse, I. (2 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - First Draft: Faulkner and His Muse, II. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - “The Decline of Joseph Conrad’s Creative Powers” (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Student Papers on Faulkner (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Marianne DeKoven-Reappointment/Promotion, 1990 (1 of 2) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Marianne DeKoven-Reappointment/Promotion, 1990 (2 of 2) (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - “Conrad in Conflict,” by Moser, circa 1940s (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - “Wyatt’s Reputation as a Poet,” by Moser, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Harvard Library Bulletin, 1956 and Conrad MSS (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - MSS “Chapter One: The Progenitor (First Draft), I” (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - MSS “Chapter One: The Progenitor (First Draft), II” (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Garnett/Conrad (Miscellaneous) (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Partial Faulkner MSS (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2012-083
  - Datebooks, 1971-1979 (Box 1)
  - French Novel (research notes) (Box 2)
  - Department/University, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Department/University, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Ford Stuff (correspondence re publishing) (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Guggenheim Foundation (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Xu Chengshi (1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Xu Chengshi (2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1953-1989 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Undergrads '00, circa 2000 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Personal, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Overseas Centers (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Continuing Studies, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Simpson Book Fund (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Library Book Fund, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Conrad Photographs (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Door Nameplates (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Quotations (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Gradebooks (restricted), circa 1953-1996 (Box 4)
  - Promotion and Tenure files (restricted) (Box 5)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2014-002
  - Current Grad. Stud., 1971-1974 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Friends and Colleagues, 1971-1974 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Candidates (correspondence, chiefly), 1971-1974 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Undergrads, 1971-1974 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Business (not personal), 1971-1974 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Former Grad Students, 1971-1974 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Current Undergrads, 1974-1979 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Former Undergrads, 1974-1979 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Current Grads I, 1974-1979 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Current Grads II, 1974-1979 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Current Grads III, 1974-1979 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Former Grads, 1974-1979 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Colleages/ Friends I, 1974-1979 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Colleages/ Friends II, 1974-1979 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Colleagues/Friends III, 1974-1979 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Business, 1974-1979 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Dept./University, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Dept./University and Resumes, 1983- (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Former Graduates, 1980- (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Former Undergraduates, 1980- (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Former Undergraduates II, 1980-1982 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Current Undergraduates, 1980-1983 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Current Grad Students, 1980-1983 (?) (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Personal/Bus., 1980 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Olive, Rosettis, Kropotkin, etc (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Ford Stuff (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Department, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Department, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Department and University, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Watt, Karl, Najder, Moser, Kermode, Thorburn, Hoffman, Thornton (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Mosaic and JC: A Commemoration (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Hessler, Hoff, Cooper, De Koven, Gabbay, Webb, Oxford, Wenska, Stang (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Chance Article: Corresp., Notes, Xeroxes (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Fiction + RY/WN, 1923-1937 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Short Stories (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Ford Letters and Loeuve Coll. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Parade's End (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Ford's Non-Fiction Books, 1915-1939 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Non-Fiction, 1915 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Notions - Old (notes on notes) (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Notes on Anec and Bing Chaps, 1896-1910 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Ford's Novels, 1910-1915 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Rossette's Shifting of the Fire, 1892 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Hueffer's Peire Dival, "Joseph Conrad," Riesenberg, 1924 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Ford's Novels, 1900-1909 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - FMB and Fairy Tales, 1892 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Ford's Poetry, 1921 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Two Scandalous (Unintelligible) - Notes, 1911 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence re Conrad and Ford, 1955-1966 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Notions and Conversations, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Ford to Pinker, 1923 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Ford to Olive Garnett, 1892- (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Copies - Conrad's Letters to Ford, 1901- (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Letters from Conrad, 1890-1913 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Of Garnetts and Hueffers - Copy, 1932- (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - From Olive Garnett's Diary, 1890-1906 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Oliver Maddox Hueffer, 1892-1895 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Scraps of Xerox of Olive G., 1892-1895 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - The Hueffers and Olive, 1890-1895 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper Articles on Ford and Oliver and Francis Hueffer, 1830-1905 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Articles on Ford (Chron.), 1912- (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Violet Hunt, 1908-1922 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Books on Ford A-M, 1914-1969 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Books on Ford N-Z, 1928-1960 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Stella Bower, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Ezra Pound, 1907-1951 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - H.G. Wells, 1915-1920 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Conrad, Ford, and Sources of Chance, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Teets Review, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Drafts - Article on Olive's Diary, 1903- (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Ford to Harriet Monroe, 1913-1936 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Ford to H.G. and Mrs. Wells, 1900-1939 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Hueff Collection - Cornell, Conrad to Pinker (Berg)=Houghton-James, 1901 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Ford and Elsie, -1954 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - The Good Soldier (Ford Madox Ford) by Thomas C. Moser, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - The New Review, 1894 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - An English Context for Conrad's Russian Characters, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - The Spectator, 1909 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Unlabeled Definition Excerpts (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Preface and Chapter One, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - INDEX II Galleys 65 plus Linear List by Galleys (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - INDEX I Galleys 2-64. 153-172 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Unlabeled Family Tree, 1789-1943 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Unlabeled Loose Yellow Sheets, Book Planning (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Ford Madox Hueffer and Under Western Eyes, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Draft of "Under Olive Garnett's Eyes" I (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Draft of "Under Olive Garnett's Eyes" II (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Draft of "Under Olive Garnett's Eyes" III (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Wuthering Heights: Text, Sources, Criticism, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Shakespearean Imagination, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Conradiana, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Lord Jim and the Consequences of Kantian Autonomy, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Conrad's Lord Jim: Meditations on the Other Hemisphere, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Impressionist Painting and the Reflexive Novel of the Early Twentieth Century, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Textual Problems (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Ernie's Stuff and My Response to It (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Bonds of Empathy: The Widening Audience in Lord Jim, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - The Pink Toads in Lord Jim, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Integrity and Self-Deception, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - A Conversation on the Blood Oranges Between John Hawkes and Robert Scholes, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - On Impressionism, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - The Art of Fiction, 1888 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Conrad in the Nineteenth Century, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Emily Bronte in the Hands of Male Critics, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Wuthering Heights: Text, Sources, Criticism, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Hound & Horn: Henry James, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Sealed Envelopes addressed to Thomas Moser (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - English 179 Materials, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - The Sound and the Fury - Chronological Reconstruction (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - A William Faulkner Chronology (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - A Faulkner Geneology (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - McCaslin Geneology (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - William Faulkner: An Informat Bibliographical Guide, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Compson Geneology (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Faulkner: A Green Bough, 1933 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Faulkner Stuff, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Unlabeled Strips of Paper with Notes (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Chapters 1-6 The Fiction of Ford Maddox Ford (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Chapters 7-10 D. Levin's Vision (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Chapters 11-14 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Extra pp. of the Ford and rough drafts of geneology chronology (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Impressionism, Agorophobia, and the Good Solider, 1913-1914 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Parade's End as Christmas Pantomime, 1924-1928 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Student Evaluations, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Conrad's Russian Characters, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Comp Lit (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Old English (empty) (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Unlabeled Large Notecards with Book Citations (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Unlabeled Small Notecards with Book Citations (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Thoughts on Marwood Section (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Conrad, Ford, and Chance (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Speculations on Conrad, Marwood, and The Good Soldier (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - The New Humpty Dumpty (1912) Rough Draft (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - The Simple Life Limited Rough Draft (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - The Young Lovell, Ford's last novel before The Good Soldier Rough Draft (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - The Panel Rough Draft (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Ladies Whose Bright Eyes Rough Draft (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Unlabeled Rough Draft (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Men and Women (1909-1913) Rough Draft (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Mr. Apollo Rough Draft (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - An English Girl (1907) Rough Draft (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Unlabeled Rough Draft (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Nature Rough Draft (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - The Fifth Queen Rough Draft (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - The Benefactor Rough Draft (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Chapter Three, Men and Women Rough Draft (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Chapter Three, Men and Women, The Shifting of Refine (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Ford Madox and the Three Fairy Tales (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Stella and Last Yrs - Rough (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Bing (Rough) II (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - I Preface Chapter II (Biographical) Rough Draft (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Preface (Personal) Rough Draft (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - English 179 First Quiz (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - English 125 Tentative Schedule (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Assorted Faulkner Copies (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Honors Workshop (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - An English Context for Conrad's Russian Characters Rough Draft (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Roger Tennant (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Rough Drafts and Planning for "An English Context for Conrad's Russian Characters", 1982- (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Tennant (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Copies of Letters from Ford Madox Ford, 1908-1936 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Ford Seminar Papers (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Unlabeled Notes (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Oxford Slavonic Papers, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Victorian Studies Reponse (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Context for "Under Western Eyes" (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Assorted Printouts (Olive, Stepniak, etc) (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - New York Times Article about Stepniak, 1890 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - New York Daily Tribune Article about Stepniak, 1890 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Stepniak Lore (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - The Outlook, 1914 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Talk to Graduate Students, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Chapter 14 Citations (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Assorted Citations (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Chapter 11 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Chapter 10 Section 2 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Chapter 10 Section 4 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Chapter 10 Section 3 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Olive (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Conradiana: Conrad-Ford (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Preliminary Preface (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - The Outlook, 1914 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Chapter 10 Section 1 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Unlabeled Notes (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Unlabeled Notes II (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - The Younger Madox, 1897 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - The Good Soldier (Ford Madox Ford) by Thomas C. Moser (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Articles on Ford and Other Notes (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Parade's End and Preceding Works (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Ford to Tetley, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Ford Letters (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Chapter Four (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Chapter 2 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Thomas C. Moser Stanford-in-France (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Conrad and Ford - Version 1 of talk (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Outlook (Empty) (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - P.E. and Preceedings (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - The Life in the Fiction of Ford Maddox Ford (Box 12-13)
    Scope and Contents note
    Manuscript and galley proofs.
  - The Saddest Story manuscript (Box 13)
  - Introduction to "The Good Soldier" (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - 2nd Am. Edition - The Good Soldier, 1915 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - 1st American Edition - The Good Soldier, 1915 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Translation Stuff (Winter): L'Etranger - Second Part - Ruth Sitton, 1969 Feb 27 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Translation Stuff (Winter): "The Stranger" - Part 1, circa 1969 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Translation Stuff (Winter): "The Stranger" - Part 2, circa 1969 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Conradiana & SML Offprint, 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Sewanee Review - Views of Edwardian Fiction, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Joseph Conrad - Conradiana, 1985-1987 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Stanford Review & "Keeping Them Down on the Farm: The Future of the Humanities", 1965 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Thomas C. Moser - From Olive Garnett's Diary & Biographical Speculations on the Genesis of "The Good Soldier" (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2017-232
  - 269 - Intro on Romanticism 178 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Whitman (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Dickinson (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 269 - Local color, J. Garland (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - W.D. Howells - blog, 1837 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - A Modern Instance (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Rise of Silas Lapham (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - A Hazard of N. Fortunes (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Criticism Fiction, 1891 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Crane, RBC, MAG, "OB" (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 209 Dreiser, Carrie; C. Awakenings (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Dreiser, Sister Carrie (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Robinson - Frost Adams, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 9- Introduction + B. Franklin, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Poe (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Thoreau, Walden, 1837 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Hawthorne, S. L., S. S. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Malville, M. D. B.C. Pierre (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Whitman, Frost, Eliot, Dickinson, O'Neill (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Faulkener (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Faulkner stories, Hamlet (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Sound and Fury (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Sanctuary (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - As I Lay Dying (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Light in August (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - The Bear + Hamlet (1 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - The Bear + Hamlet (2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Ford (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 194 - Ford, Woolf, Greene, Phys., 1982 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - English I, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - English 2 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Wanderer + Prologue (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Am. Fiction, Introductions, 1917-1940 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - CATHER (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Andersen (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Fitzgerald, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Hemingway (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Steinbech (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Wright (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - West, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - English 25 - Sufice (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - English 35 - Poetry + W.S., 1963 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - English 15 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - G. G., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Conrad - Biography (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Nigger- Youth H or D (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Lord Jim + Imp (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Typhoon - Amy Foster - S. S. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Nostromd (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Secret Agent (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Hawkes + NAB (1 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Hawkes + NAB (2 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - W.S.'s Hacket (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Important + detailed comment (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Negatives (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Old Mark Twain and the Mysterious Strangers (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Tom Sawyer, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Mark Twain - Blog (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - "Old Times in the Mississippi" (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Huckleberry Finn, 1934 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Conn. Yankee Ink. A.'s court (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Pudd'n Head Wilson, 1898 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - James - biography (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - The American, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Europeans - Wash. SQ (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Portrait of a Lady + Art of Fiction (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Maisie - Spoils - PC (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Ambassadors (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Wings of the Dove, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Golden Bowl (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Short stories (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Unlabeled (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Unlabeled, 1843 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Stanford Hemingway Letters + Guerard's Review English 40-42A (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Course readers, English 187T, 1996 Fall (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Faulkner Article, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Conrad Impressionism handouts (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Faulkner Article, corrected version of 1991 draft (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - G.S. Annotation (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Good Soldier - textual changes (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Faulkner's Muse, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Conrad Impressionist Novel, 187T, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - James, Conrad, Ford, Hawkes, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - 80th Birthday (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - James Seminar, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Faulkner Article (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Faulkner Seminar, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Marwood's photograph other recollections (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Oxford Press, 1989-1999 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Faulkner article (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Conrad/Impressionist novel course reader, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - "Some Reminisces," by Thomas C. Moser (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - College on the Mississippi, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Faulkner, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Conrad Faulkner, English 388C, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Drafts notes (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Mark Twain (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Faulkner (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Notes drafts (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - William Faulkner american humor SCS Lit 113, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Three Songs by Alva Henderson (poems by Janet Lewis), 1990 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Janet Lewis - Jean Bill Lane lecture, 1990 Nov 5 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Dept. of English newsletters, 1996-2000 (Box 6, Folder 31)